

CONTACT ME AT

- B-1/160 A, New Ashok Nagar, New Delhi -110096
- aleemakhtar57@gmail.com
- +919582284886
- in @aleemakhtar57

SKILLS SUMMARY

- UI Design
- User Flow
- Wireframe
- HTML5/CSS3
- SASS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- WordPress
- Shopify
- Magento Theming

TOOLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- Jira

MOHD ALEEM AKHTAR

SR FRONTEND DEVELOPER(UI/UX)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Over all 10+ years of experience in user interface design and web application development. Strong Experience in frontend technology likes (HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery), PHP CMS Theming like (WordPress, Woocommerce, Shopify, Magento), PSD and PSD to HTML.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

Narana Tech | Sep 2017 - present

- Create layout for the website and forward to client for the approval.
- Create HTML/CSS/JS and Integrate in the Magento
- Create HTML and Develop the Wordpress website
- Work on the Shopify project

Frontend Developer

Conceptol | Aug 2014 - Sept 2017

- Create layout for the website and forward to client for the approval.
- Create HTML and Integrate in the Magento
- Create HTML and Develop the Wordpress website
- Work directly in the Magento template.

Web Designer

Robo Consulting | Nov 2013 - Aug 2014

- Demonstrated consistent hard work and dedication to achieve results and improve operations.
- Create HTML from the PDF and Develp the Wordpress website

Web Designer

Technologus | Oct 2012 - Nov 2013

- Achieved service time and quality targets.
- Produced high-volume orders to effectively meet customer demand
- Create HTML from the PDF and Develp the Wordpress website

INTERESTS

Interest & Hobbies : Listening to soft music

LANGUAGES

• English & Hindi

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University, formerly UPTU MCA | 2009 - 2012 Pass with 76.2%

Veer Bahadur Singh Purvanchal University BCA | 2006 - 2009 Pass with 65.8%

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATES

- Six month Project Training From HEADSTRONG INDIA PVT LTD, Noida.
- Diploma in Business Computing from C-DAC, Pune.
- Certification in JAVA (Core java, J2EE) from Tech Mentro, Noida.

LIVE PROJECTS

Magento projects

https://mumandyou.com https://www.purefruittechnologies.com

Wordpress Projects

https://www.nationalach.com

https://www.zeopto.com

http://cricrain.com

http://www.3sensesclinic.com

https://www.fieldassist.com

https://www.digitalinfusion.in

https://teambattle.dk

https://jonthebarber.com

http://ricebeltofficials.com

Shopify Projects

https://captainzack.in

https://sensbodycare.com

https://mumandyou.us

https://pettofoods.com